T.S. Gold Family Papers 1982.0002
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series III: Newspapers, 1800-1901
  - The Independent (Box 17:, Folder 251)
    - 1867 November 8
    - 1867 November 28
    - 1895 April 4
  - Litchfield Enquirer (Box OS, 18:, Folder 252-253)
    - 1832 December 27
    - 1858 June 10
    - 1867 December 19
    - 1894 March 14
    - 1902 November 6
    - 1902 November 13
    - 1904 June 16
  - The Manchester Union, 1901 November 20 (Box 18:, Folder 254)
  - Massachusetts Ploughman (Box 18:, Folder 255)
    - 1881 July 30
    - 1894 October 13
    - 1894 October 20
  - The Monitor, 1800 January (Box 18:, Folder 256)
  - The New England Homestead (Box 18:, Folder 257)
    - 1883 March 31
    - 1883 November 17
    - 1884 February 16
    - 1884 August 23
    - 1891 March 21
  - The New Haven Palladium, 1882 October 14 (Box 18:, Folder 258)
  - The Newton Bee, 1881 December 23 (Box 18:, Folder 259)
  - The New York Herald, 1891 February 1 (Box 18:, Folder 260)
  - New York Observer, 1829 March 14 (Box OS)
  - New York Observer, 1884 June 26 (Box OS:, Folder 261)
  - Norwalk Gazette, 1873 July 15 (Box OS:, Folder 262)
  - Pall Mall Gazette, 1892 April 4 (Box OS:, Folder 263)
  - The Philadelphia Press, 1895 November 27 (Box OS:, Folder 264)
  - The Religious Herald (Box OS:, Folder 265)
    - 1879 December 4
    - 1880 November 4
    - 1892 November 10
    - 1892 December 22
  - The Republic, 1859 October 29 (Box OS:, Folder 266)
  - The Republican Standard, 1865 April 21 (Box OS:, Folder 267)
  - The Republican Standard, 1867 December 20
  - Sacramento Daily Record - Union, 1889 November 13 - 21; (9 issues) (Box OS)
  - The Sag Harbor Express (Box OS)
    - 1890 June 19
    - 1895 September 19
    - 1895 October 10
    - 1895 October 17
    - 1895 October 24
    - 1895 October 31
    - 1896 August 20
    - 1901 January 31
  - Tolland County Leader, 1890 December 11 (Box OS)
  - Ulster County Gazette [reprint], 1800 January 4 (Box OS:, Folder 268)
  - Ulster County Gazette, 1899 February 10
  - Waterbury American, 1899 February 17 (Box OS:, Folder 269)
  - Waterbury American, 1899 March 3 (Box OS:, Folder 270)
  - The Wellesley Courant, 1883 March 23 (Box OS:, Folder 271)
  - The Winsted Herald, 1877 Nov 20 (Box OS:, Folder 272)
  - The Winsted Herald, 1882 Sep 15
  - The World, 1872 September 4 (Box OS:, Folder 273)
  - The World, 1972 September 8